在采访过程中的某个时候，
At the some point in
the interview process,
你得做个电话屏幕或者密码测试
you're going to have to do probably
a phone screen or a code test.
我之前采访过的很多公司都在做手机屏幕，因为它是
A lot of companies that I've interviewed
before do phone screens because it's
有一个很好的机会让一个工程师去找另一个工程师
a good chance to have an engineer
talk to another engineer.
通常都是通过视频，或者可能只是通过电话。
So usually it's over video or
it might just be over telephone.
但是，实际上，这是一种机会，可以在双方都能接触到第一次接触。
But, really, it's a chance to kind of
meet your first reach out on both sides.
你要和你一起工作的人见面
You meet the kind of person
you're gonna be working with.
你会遇到的，你也会理解他们会问什么样的问题。
You meet and you kind of understand
what sort of questions do they ask.
他们怎么说问题
How do they word questions?
他们有多友好
How friendly are they?
他们在很多问题上都在开玩笑，就像放松一样吗 ?
Do they joke around a lot,
and like kind of relax?
他们是非常，非常僵硬，而且因书的不同而不同。
Are they very, very stiff and
vary by the book.
这些事情都要靠自己来做
And all these things will depend and
it's a good chance for
你作为候选人去感受公司的感觉
you as the candidates to get a feel for
the company,
作为采访者找到候选人的感觉是一个很好的机会。
it's a good chance as the interviewer
to get a feel for the candidate.
他们密码的时候他们就放心了吗
Are they at ease when they code?
他们放松了吗
Are they relaxed?
但希望你能把手机屏幕的选项给他们密码测试
But hopefully, you'll give them the option
of the phone screen to code test.
很多时候，我更喜欢电话屏幕，我们就能得到它。
A lot of times, I prefer the phone screen,
we get right to it.
我不会再花时间做密码测试了
I don't spend any extra of
my time doing code test.
通常，电话屏幕显示 30 分钟到一个小时，在那里的某个地方。
Phone screens generally, say 30 minutes
to an hour, somewhere in there.
他们做的是实时编码。
And they're done live coding.
所以有些人有些紧张
So, some people that get a little nervous,
实践这些我们要做的事情很不错
it's good to practice these things
which we're gonna do in a little bit.
但是真正的让神经脱离生命的代码对我们来说是很有帮助的
But really kind of get the nerves out life
code it's really helpful to kind of see
在我给手机屏幕的时候，有人通过一个问题来工作。
how someone works through a problem
when I'm giving a phone screen.
作为手机屏幕的候选人，当你在中间的时候会问问题。
As the candidate for phone screen, when
you're in the middle of it ask questions.
我真的希望有人问我这样的问题，我能做到吗 ?
I really want someone to ask me
questions like hey, can I do this?
要我这么做吗
Should I do this?
这是正确的做法吗 ?
Is this the right way?
现在的问题并不太多我只是在为你解决这个问题
Not too many questions for it's like well
now I'm just solving the problem for you.
但我希望有人问我真实生活的问题
But I want someone to ask me questions
cuz that's how it is in real life.
没有人分配您的项目，就像祝你在一个月内好运。
No one assigns your projects and
like good luck see you in a month.
不你有对话我想让你和我一起
No, you have the dialogue and
that's what I want it with the coterie and
你应该试着跟采访者建立联系
that's what you should try to
establish with the interviewer.
他们是否有所帮助?
Are they helpful?
或者他们被开除了
Or are they dismissive.
他们是友好和外向的，你就像，我知道，电话屏幕很烂，
Are they friendly and outgoing, you're
like, I understand, phone screens suck,
面试很烂
interviews suck.
他们很友好，或者总是这样，这是浪费我的时间，
And they're friendly, or there always
like, this is a waste of my time,
真不敢相信我这么做
I can't believe I'm doing this.
这个人为什么不明白我在说什么
Why, doesn't this person
understand what I'm talking about?
这些都是你在电话屏幕里要审查的东西，所以问问题。
These are things you should vet out during
the phone screen, so ask questions.
解决你的问题，特别是如果你被困住了。
Talk out your solution,
especially if you get stuck.
它对任何人都没有帮助。
It does not help anybody.
如果你坐在你的脑袋里
If you're sitting there
thinking inside your head.
你要在采访中大声说出来
You have to talk out
loud in any interview.
这就是你想在这里建立我的方式
That's what you have to do you
want to establish here's how I'm
思考一个问题。
thinking about a problem.
你也许是绝对正确的面试说的不错的想法
And you might be absolutely right
the interview say yeah, good thinking.
是啊不我觉得你是在正确的道路上
Yeah, no,
I think you're on the right path here or
他们可能就像你离开的时候一样
they might be like you're way off course.
你在思考这个问题的方式是完全错误的。
And the way you're thinking about
the problem is completely wrong.
这是一种更好的思考方式。
And here's a better way to think about it.
但不管怎么说除非你大声说话
But either way, you can't get
there unless you talk out loud and
说说你是怎么想这个问题的
talk about how you're
thinking about the problem.
并且在环境中感到舒适。
And get comfortable in the environment.
如果使用代码笔或代码测试，其中有很多。
If using code pen or code tests,
there's a lot of them.
提前问吧
Ask ahead of time,
他们会向你传达一个你要使用的环境的链接
they'll generally send you a link to
the environment you're gonna be using.
他们会说这是一个 CodePen 链接，或者类似的东西。
They'll say it's a CodePen link,
or something like that.
请放心，了解该处的调试方案。
Get comfortable,
understand the debugging scenario there.
某些环境，您可以调试。
Some environments, you can debug.
一些环境，对调试很有挑战性。
Some environments,
it's challenging to debug.
但你知道吗你要把密码活活吗
But understand that,
are you gonna be running the code live?
它会输出什么东西，还是只是，他们想知道你是怎么编码的吗 ?
Is it gonna output something, or
is it just, they wanna see how you code?
这不一定是可以执行的。
That's not necessarily
gonna be executable.
作为手机屏幕的采访者，你在一个安静的地方吗 ?
As the interviewer for the phone screen,
are you in a quiet area?
在一个安静的地方是很尊敬的，他们花了一个小时的时间
Being in a quiet area is just respectful,
they took an hour of the day as busy
做这个手机屏幕的人至少能给他们安静点的东西
people to do this phone screen the least
you can do is give them something quiet,
没有人在后台找到乒乓球
not people find ping
pong in the background.
有一次我接到一个可怕的电话，这不是电话屏幕，
I once had a terrible call and
this wasn't the phone screen,
这是招聘者，但是我就像，我几乎听不见你。
this was recruiter, but
I was like, I can barely hear you.
就像，我的名字叫什么，什么，什么，什么，什么，什么，什么，什么，什么，
It's like, my name's blah, blah,
blah I'm with blah, blah, blah company.
我听不见你的声音
I'm like, I can't hear you.
抱歉我们工作得太辛苦了
Sorry we're in a WeWork.
我喜欢很酷我们和玻璃墙一起工作
I'm like, cool,
we work with the glass walls.
但那不是我的问题
But that's not my problem.
你的工作就是跟我谈话至少你能做的就是
Your job is to have this conversation
with me, the least you could do is
在一个安静的地方我能听到你说话
be respectful and
be in a quiet area where I can hear you.
这不太不合理 [ LAUGH]。
That's not too unreasonable [LAUGH].
而在他们的电话屏幕上唯一的问题是，问题的措辞是否正确 ?
And the only thing to ask on their phone
screen is, is the problem well worded?
他们要花 15 分钟还是要花 15 分钟
Are they gonna spend 15 minutes or are you
gonna spend 15 minutes of that an hour or
有 45 分钟向他们解释问题吗
45 minute time explaining
the problem to them?
如果是这样，这可能不是一个好问题。
If so, that's probably not a good problem.
他们要做的事情应该是很清楚的，很简练的，
They should be very clear and
very concise about what they need to do,
他们需要执行的事情你要找的是什么
what they need to execute on,
what you're looking for.
最理想的是两分钟最多
Ideally, two three minutes at most.
这应该是一个很直接的问题。
It should be a very
straightforward problem.
候选人是否知道需求和限制是什么 ?
Does the candidate know what
the requirements and restrictions are?
你有没有说过，你不能用 jQuery ，你不能用 React，
Did you say hey, you can't use jQuery,
you can't use React,
你不能用任何图书馆
you can't use any libraries.
这只是单纯的香草 JavaScript
It's just pure vanilla JavaScript.
或者，你可以进口任何你想要的东西，不管做什么。
Or hey, you can import whatever you want,
whatever gets the job done.
但候选人是否知道呢 ?
But does the candidate know that?
确保他们知道你什么时候接受采访
Make sure they know when you're
giving that interview or
你给了一个手机屏幕你到底在找什么
you're given a phone screen,
what exactly you're looking for.
你最后还是请假了 ?
And did you leave time for
question at the end?
你应该总是在最后的时候留到问题的时候
You should always leave time for
question at the end, always.
同样地，你甚至没有试图建立。
Again, you're not even
trying to establish.
他们能解决这个问题吗 ?
Can they solve this problem?
我们想知道他们是怎么想的
We're trying to understand
how do they think?
他们是否有能力搬去外面的世界 ?
Are they capable of moving
on to the outside world?
我们会建立，他们能解决这些问题吗 ?
We'll establish,
can they solve these problems?
我们真正想的是他们如何看待一个问题
What we're really trying to get to
how they think about a problem,
他们怎么处理这个问题，他们会问很多这样的问题吗 ?
how they approach it, do they ask
a lot of questions things like that.
但正是这些对话，所以对话就需要以另一种方式进行。
But it's these dialogue, so the dialogue
needs to go back the other way.
结束提问的时间。
Leaves time for questions at the end.
如果你想不重要我们还有 45 分钟
Make sure it doesn't matter if you're
like, we got 45 minutes and so
我们没时间了
we ran out of time.
这也是关于尊重的问题。
Again, it's about respect.
是关于同理心的。
It's about empathy.
如果我跟一个想知道的人说话
If I'm talking to someone I want to know,
well,
你在公司工作多久了
how long have you been at the company?
我想知道证交会是什么
I want to know what the SEC is.
你是哪个队的
What team are you on?
你都是 UI 工程师吗
Are you even the UI engineer,
它们可能不是您可能获得一般一般工程问题的时候。
oftentimes they may not be you might get
a generic general engineering question.
你可能有个前端的问题
You might get a front end question.
可能是他们第一次使用手机屏幕。
It might be someone that it's their
first time giving a phone screen.
这些都是，但你想再给点问题时间，因为再一次，
All these things, but you wanna give time
for questions at the end because again,
是关于两个人之间的对话
it's about the dialogue
between two people.
嗯。
Yes.
>> 作为候选人询问采访者的良好做法是否良好
&gt;&gt; Is it good practice as a candidate
to ask the interviewer what type of
他们会问吗
questions they're gonna ask?
>> 是。
&gt;&gt; Yes.
我们会在现场讨论这个问题。
And we'll talk about that for the on-site.
电话屏幕他们可能不会告诉你或者他们会告诉你
The phone screen, they may not tell you or
they might tell you.
我知道这对我毫无帮助
I know it's not helpful at all.
有些公司会说，嘿，这是一个正面的焦点问题，
Some companies will say, hey,
it's a frontend focus question so
你会做点什么的
you're gonna be building something.
或者他们会说这是普通的 CS 问题
Or they might say,
it's a general CS problem,
一种泄漏的代码样式一般 CS 问题解决方法。
kind of a leaked code style
general CS problem solving.
这不是什么语言
It doesn't what's the language.
但那是个很棒的问题，问我能用什么语言来编码 ?
But that's a great question,
asked what language can I code in?
有些地方，他们就像我们的问题在 Python中。
Some places,
they're like our problem is in Python.
我很酷，我不做 Python ，我是一个 JavaScript 工程师。
I'm like cool, I don't do Python,
I'm a JavaScript engineer.
但那是个大问题你应该提前问这个问题
But that's a great question you
should ask this ahead of time.
通常你会有两类问题
And generally you gonna
get two types of problems,
他们就会在那里或附近
they're gonna CS style general
Leech ODZ medium around there or
你会得到具体的 UI 问题比如建造轮播之类的
your gonna get specific UI problems like
build carousel or something like that.
我想是 45 分钟吧
Which, 45 minutes, I think?